FACTS WHAT DOES RIVER WORKS CREDIT UNION DO WITHYOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Why? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. FederalLaw gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal lawalso requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personalinformation. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

What? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product orservice you have with us.This information can include:• Social Security Number and income• Account Balances and payment history• Credit History and Credit ScoresWhen you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information asdescribed in this notice.

How? All Financial companies need to share customer’s personal information to runtheir everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financialcompanies can share their customer’s personal information; the reasons RiverWorks Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

Questions? Call (781) 599-0096, 800-367-1207 or go towww.rwcu.com

Reason we can shareyour personal information

For Everyday Business Purposes

Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s),respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to creditbureaus.

For our marketing purposes

To offer our products and services to you.

For joint marketing with other financial institutions.For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes

Information about your transactions and experiences.

For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes

Information about your creditworthiness.

For our affiliates to market to you.

For non affiliates to market to you.

Does River WorksCredit Union Share?Can youlimit thissharing?YES

YES

YESNO

NO

YES

NO

NO

NO

NOWE DON’T SHARE

WE DON’T SHARE

YES

WE DON’T SHARE

Rev. November 2022

To limitour sharing

• Call 800-367-1207 our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) or• Visit us online: www.rwcu.comPlease note:If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information [30] days fromthe date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continueto share your information as described in this notice.However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

947 Western AvenueLynn, MA 01905

Who we areWho is providing this notice? RIVER WORKS CREDIT UNION

What we do

How does River Works Credit Unionprotect my personal information?

How does River Works Credit Unioncollect my personal information?

Why can’t I limit all sharing?

Definitions

Affiliates

Nonaffiliates

Joint Marketing

Other Important Information

State Law - If you give us written permission to share your information about electronic funds transfers.

Bankers Group Purchasing, Waltham, MA 02453 1-781-891-0303 (Rev. 11/22)-38405

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use,we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measuresinclude computer safeguards and secured files and buildings

We collect your personal information, for example, when you;• open an account or deposit money• pay your bills or apply for a loan• use your credit or debit cardWe also collect your personal information from others, such as creditbureaus, affiliates or other companies.

Federal law gives you the right to limit only• sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes - informationabout your creditworthiness• affiliates from using your information to market to you• sharing for non-affiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights tolimit sharing.(See below for more on your rights under state law).

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can befinancial or non-financial companies.• River Works Insurance Group LLC

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can befinancial or non-financial companies.• Nonaffiliates we share with can include Insurance Companies.

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies thattogether market financial products or services to you.• Our joint marketing partners include Insurance Companies.
